The devil you know.
Renegade is a western film directed by Jan Kounen.
U.S Marshal Mike Donovan has dark memories of the death of his first love.
He keeps peace between the Americans and the natives who had
temporarily adopted and taken care of him.
The evil actions of a white sorcerer lead him to confront the villain in the Sacred Mountains, and, through
shamanic rituals conquer his fears and uncover a suppressed memory he would much rather deny.
Mike Blueberry, played by Vincent Cassel.
Maria Sullivan, played by Juliette Lewis.
Runi, played by Temuera Morrison.
Rolling Star, played by Ernest Borgnine.
Woodhead, played by Djimon Hounsou.
Young Mike Blueberry, played by Hugh O'Conor.
Bo Bragason (born 27 March 2004) is an English actress.
On television, she is known for her roles in the BBC One series Three Girls
(2017), The Jetty (2024) and the Disney+ series Renegade Nell (2024).
Her films include The Radleys (2024).
She is set to star as Princess Zelda in an upcoming
film adaptation of The Legend of Zelda.
The film explores themes of magic, indian territory,
marshal, native american, based on comic.
The tone is dark.